Karen Shearer Collection, 1935-1996, bulk 1974-1992
Indiana University Digital Library Program
- 1. Special Edition (radio program), 1975-1994
  - 1.4. Special Edition Artist Photographs, 1979-1994, 907 photographs: b&w; 8 x 10 in.
    - Cameo, 1988, PA 2764
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000123
    - Camp
      SEE: Anthony & the Camp
    - Campbell, Tevin, 1993, PA 2765
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000124
    - Carey, Mariah, 1991, PA 2766
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000125
    - Carey, Mariah, 1990, PA 2767
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000126
    - Carlton, Carl, circa 1982, PA 2768
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000127
    - Carman, Pauli, 1986, PA 2769
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000128
    - Carman, Pauli, 1987, PA 2770
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000129
      1987 September
    - Chaka Khan
      SEE: Quincy Jones: Back on the Block
    - Champaign, circa 1984, PA 2771
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000130
    - Chancler, Ndugu
      SEE: Ndugu & the Chocolate Jam Co.
    - Chapman, Tracy, 1989, PA 2772
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000131
    - Chapter 8, 1988, PA 2773
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000132
    - Charles, Ray, 1993, PA 2774
      SEE ALSO: Quincy Jones: Back on the Block
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000133
    - Charvoni, 1989, PA 2775
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000134
    - Cherry, Ava, 1987, PA 2776
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000135
    - Chi-Lites, circa 1983, PA 2777
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000136
    - Chimes, 1989, PA 2778
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000137
    - Chocolate Jam Co.
    - Christopher, Gavin, 1988, PA 2779
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000138
      1988 March
    - Chuck Berry Hail! Hail! Rock 'N' Roll
      "Chuck Berry Hail Hail Rock 'n' Roll" is a Delilah Films Production/A Taylor Hackford Film staring Chuck Berry and featuring such recording greats as Eric Clapton, Robert Cray, Etta James, Julian Lennon, Keith Richards and Linda Ronstadt. Keith Richards produced the music for the Universal Release, which was produced by Stephanie Bennett and directed by Taylor Hackford.
      - Chuck Berry Hail! Hail! Rock 'N' Roll, 1987, PA 2703
        Group portrait of Bo Diddley, Little Richard, Chuck Berry and director Taylor Hackford.
        http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000060
      - Chuck Berry Hail! Hail! Rock 'N' Roll, 1987, PA 2704
        [Top]: Chuck Berry joined on stage by Julian Lennon and Ingrid Berry, and [Bottom] Chuck Berry backs Etta James with one of his trademark guitar riffs.
        http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000061
      - Chuck Berry Hail! Hail! Rock 'N' Roll, 1987, PA 2705
        Director Taylor Hackford.
        http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000062
      - Chuck Berry Hail! Hail! Rock 'N' Roll, 1987, PA 2705b
        Linda Ronstadt and Julian Lennon offer their own interpretations of Chuck Berry's "Living in the U.S.A." and Johnny B. Goode."
        http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000063
      - Chuck Berry Hail! Hail! Rock 'N' Roll, 1987, PA 2706
        Chuck Berry in a festive mood with friends Johnny Johnson and Julian Lennon.
        http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000064
      - Chuck Berry Hail! Hail! Rock 'N' Roll, 1987, PA 2708
        Chuck Berry performs one of his classic hits in this scene from "Chuck Berry Hail! Hail! Rock 'N' Roll."
        http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000066
      - Chuck Berry Hail! Hail! Rock 'N' Roll, 1987, PA 2709
        Chuck Berry's spirited performance at his 60th birthday concert in St. Louis is one of the many highlights of "Chuck Berry Hail! Hail! Rock 'N' Roll."
        http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000067
      - Chuck Berry Hail! Hail! Rock 'N' Roll, 1987, PA 2710
        Robert Cray and Joey Spampinato play in the all-star back-up band formed by Keith Richards.
        http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000068
      - Chuck Berry Hail! Hail! Rock 'N' Roll, 1987, PA 2710b
        Etta James and Eric Clapton are among the musical guests who appear on stage at the historic Fox Theatre in St. Louis.
        http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000069
    - Chuck Berry Rock 'n Roll Rarities, circa 1986, PA 2707
      Chuck Berry album cover for "Rock 'n' Roll Rarities."
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000065
    - Cinema, circa 1988, PA 2780
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000139
      1988 April
    - Clapton, Eric
      SEE: Chuck Berry Hail! Hail! Rock 'n' Roll Tribute to Curtis Mayfield
    - Clarke, Stanley, 1991, PA 2781
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000140
    - Clarke, Stanley and George Duke, 1990, PA 2782
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000141
    - Clegg, Johnny & Savuka, 1990, PA 2783
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000142
    - Clegg, Johnny & Savuka, 1988, PA 2784
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000143
    - Clegg, Johnny & Savuka, 1990, PA 2785
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000144
    - Clegg, Johnny & Savuka, 1987, PA 2786
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000145
    - Clegg, Johnny & Savuka, 1988, PA 2787
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000146
    - Clemons, Clarence, circa 1983, PA 2788
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000147
    - Clemons, Clarence, circa 1983, PA 2789
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000148
    - Clemons, Clarence, 1989, PA 2790
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000149
    - Clemons, Clarence, 1985, PA 2791
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000150
    - Cliff, Jimmy, 1985, PA 2792
      Robin Williams and Jimmy Cliff, from the Warner Brothers motion picture, "Club Paradise."
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000151
    - Clinton, George, 1982, PA 2793
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000152
    - Clinton, George, 1986, PA 2794
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000153
      1986 November
    - Clinton, George, 1989, PA 2795
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000154
      1989 January
    - Club Nouveau, 1989, PA 2796
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000155
    - Club Nouveau, 1986, PA 2797
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000156
    - Club Nouveau, 1988, PA 2798
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000157
    - Cole, Nat King, circa 1960s, PA 2799
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000158
    - Cole, Natalie, 1987, PA 2800
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000159
    - Cole, Natalie, 1987, PA 2801
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000160
    - Cole, Natalie, 1989, PA 2802
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000161
    - Cole, Natalie, 1981, PA 2803
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000162
      1981 January
    - Coleman, Desiree, circa 1988, PA 2804
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000163
    - Collage, circa 1985, PA 2805
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000164
    - Collins, Bootsy, 1988, PA 2806
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000001
    - Commodores, circa 1980s, PA 2807
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000165
    - Commodores, circa 1986, PA 2808
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000166
    - Connors, Norman, 1988, PA 2809
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000167
    - Controllers, 1989, PA 2810
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000168
    - Controllers, circa 1987, PA 2811
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000169
    - Controllers, circa 1980s, PA 2812
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000170
    - Cooper, Michael, 1989, PA 2813
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000171
    - Cooper, Michael, 1987, PA 2814
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000172
    - Cosby, Bill, 1986, PA 2815
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000173
    - Costa, Cal
    - Crawford, Randy, undated, PA 2819
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000177
    - Crawford, Randy, undated, PA 2820
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000178
    - Crawford, Randy, circa 1990, PA 2816
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000174
    - Crawford, Randy, 1993, PA 2817
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000175
    - Crawford, Randy, 1989, PA 2818
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000176
    - Cray, Robert, 1988, PA 2821 (Box 36)
      SEE ALSO: Chuck Berry Hail! Hail! Rock 'n' Roll
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000179
      1988 September
    - Crouch, Andraé, 1994, PA 2822
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000180
      1994
    - Crusaders, circa 1981, PA 2828
      SEE ALSO: Felder, Wilton, Hooper, Stix, and Sample, Joe
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000187
      1981 May
    - Crusaders, circa 1986, PA 2829
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000188
    - Crusaders, circa 1980s, PA 2831
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000190
    - Cult Jam
      SEE: Lisa Lisa and Cult Jam
    - Cymone, Andre, 1983, PA 2833
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000192
    - Cyrille, Andrew, 1992, PA 2834
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000193
    - D. J. Polo
      SEE: Kool G. & D.J. Polo
    - "D" Train, circa 1982, PA 2835
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000194
    - "D" Train, circa 1980s, PA 2836
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000195
    - Daim, Lushus, circa 1986, PA 2838
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000197
    - Dan Reed Network, 1988, PA 2839
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000198
    - D'Arby, Terence Trent, 1989, PA 2840
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000199
    - Dash, Sarah, 1988, PA 2841
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000200
    - Davis, Don, undated, PA 2842
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000201
    - Davis, Miles, 1986, PA 2843
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000202
    - Davis, Miles, 1985, PA 2844
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000203
    - Davis, Rainy, 1988, PA 2845
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000204
    - Davy D., 1987, PA 2846
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000205
    - Day, Morris, 1988, PA 2847
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000206
    - Dazz Band, circa 1986, PA 2848
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000207
      1986 August
    - Dazz Band, circa 1980s, PA 2849
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000208
    - Dazz Band, 1986, PA 2850
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000209
    - DeBarge, circa 1989, PA 2851
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000210
    - DeBarge, El, circa 1986, PA 2852
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000211
      1986 May
    - DeBarge, El, circa 1989, PA 2853
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000212
    - Dee, Mark, 1990 March, PA 2854
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000213
    - Deele, circa 1984, PA 2855
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000214
    - Def Con 4, 1990, PA 2856
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000215
    - DeFrancesco, Joey, 1991, PA 2857
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000216
      1991 February
    - DeFrancesco, Joey, 1991, PA 2858
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000217
    - DiMeola, Al, 1987, PA 2859
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000218
    - Dirty Dozen Brass Band, 1993, PA 2860
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000219
    - Dixon, Willie, 1988, PA 2861
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000220
    - Djavan, 1988, PA 2862
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000221
    - Djavan, 1985, PA 2863
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000222
    - Doc Box & B. Fresh, circa 1990, PA 2864
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000223
    - Doo Rags
      SEE: Process & the Doo Rags
    - Dorsey, Gail, 1989, PA 2865
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000224
    - D'Rivera, Paquito, 1986, PA 2866
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000225
      1986 January
    - Duke, George
      SEE: Clarke, Stanley and George Duke
    - Dulfer, Candy, circa 1990s, PA 2867
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000226
    - Dyer, Ian, 1993, PA 2868
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000227
    - Dynasty, 1982, PA 2869
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000228
    - E., Sheila (Escovedo), 1991, PA 2870
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000229
    - Earth, Wind & Fire, 1990, PA 2871
      SEE ALSO: White, Maurice
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000230
    - Earth, Wind & Fire, 1987, PA 2872
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000231
    - Earth, Wind & Fire, 1987, PA 2873
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000232
    - Earth, Wind & Fire, 1983, PA 2874
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000233
    - Earth, Wind & Fire, 1980, PA 2875
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000234
    - Emotions, 1979, PA 2877
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000236
    - England, Colin, circa 1991, PA 2878
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000237
    - Eramus Hall, 1984, PA 2938
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000299
      1984
    - Escovedo, Sheila
      SEE: E., Sheila (Escovedo)
    - Esquerita, circa 1990, PA 2879
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000238
    - Estus, Deon, 1988, PA 2880
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000239
    - Everyday People, 1990, PA 2881
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000240
    - Fassie, Brenda, 1990, PA 2883
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000242
    - Fassie, Brenda, 1990, PA 2884
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000243
    - Fassie, Brenda & the Big Dudes, circa 1991, PA 2882
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000241
    - Fat Boys, circa 1987, PA 2885
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000244
    - Fela Anikulapo Kuti, 1987, PA 2886
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000245
    - Felder, Wilton, circa 1980, PA 2825
      SEE ALSO: Crusaders
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000183
      1980 September
    - Felder, Wilton, circa 1980s, PA 2887
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000246
    - Felder, Wilton, 1983 March, PA 2823
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000181
    - Fields, Richard "Dimples", 1987, PA 2888
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000247
    - Fields, Richard "Dimples", circa 1983, PA 2888b
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000248
    - Fishbone, 1993, PA 2889
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000249
    - Fit, circa 1988, PA 2890
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000250
    - Fitzgerald, Ella
    - Five Star, 1990, PA 2891
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000251
    - Flack, Roberta
      SEE: Bryson, Peabo and Roberta Flack
    - Force M.D.'s, 1987, PA 2892
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000252
    - Force M.D.'s, 1987, PA 2892b
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000253
    - Force M.D.'s, circa 1988, PA 2893
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000254
      1988 May
    - Force M.D.'s, 1986, PA 2894
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000255
      1986 February
    - Ford, Penny, 1993, PA 2895
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000256
    - Foster, Ian, circa 1987, PA 2896
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000257
    - Four Tops, circa 1980s, PA 2897
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000258
    - Four Tops, circa 1982, PA 2898
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000259
    - Foxxx, Freddie, 1989 September, PA 2899
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000260
    - Franklin, Aretha, circa 1987, PA 2900
      SEE ALSO: Tribute to Curtis Mayfield
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000261
    - Franklin, Aretha, undated, PA 2901
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000262
    - Franklin, Aretha, circa 1983, PA 2902
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000263
    - Full Force, 1989, PA 2903
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000264
    - Full Force, 1986, PA 2904
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000265
    - Full Force, 1986, PA 2905
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000266
    - Full Force, 1985, PA 2906
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000267
    - Gable, Eric, 1989, PA 2907 (Box 37)
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000268
    - Gap Band, 1989, PA 2908
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000269
    - Garrett, Siedah, 1988, PA 2909
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000270
      1988 June
    - Gatling, Timmy, 1989, PA 2910
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000271
    - Gaye, Marvin, 1982, PA 2911
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000272
    - Gaye, Marvin, 1983 March 11, PA 2912
      Marvin Gaye greets Julio Iglesias backstage on opening night of Julio's sold-out 3-night stand at Universal Amphitheater.
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000273
      1983 March
    - Gaye, Marvin, 1983, PA 2913
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000274
    - General Caine, 1982, PA 2914
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000275
      1978/1988
    - General Kane, circa 1987, PA 2915
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000276
    - Genius, 1991, PA 2916
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000277
    - Georgio, 1987 or 1988, PA 2917
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000278
    - Gil, Gilberto
    - Gill, Johnny, circa 1990, PA 2918
      SEE ALSO: Murphy, Eddie
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000279
    - Gladys Knight and the Pips
      SEE: Knight, Gladys and the Pips
    - Glover, Bobby, 1984, PA 2922
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000283
    - Gold, Greg
      SEE: Murphy, Eddie
    - Good Girls, 1989, PA 2923
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000284
    - Grandmaster Flash, 1988, PA 2924
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000285
    - Grant, Eddy, 1986, PA 2925
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000286
    - Grant, Eddy, circa 1980s, PA 2926
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000287
    - Gray, Dobie, 1987, PA 2927
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000288
    - Green, Al, circa 1980s, PA 2928
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000289
    - Green, Al, circa 1987, PA 2929
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000290
    - Grimes, Clyde, circa 1986, PA 3452
      SEE ALSO: Untouchables
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000817
    - Guinn, circa 1986, PA 2930
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000291
    - Gumbs, Onaje Allan, circa 1988, PA 2931
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000292
    - Guthrie, Gwen, circa 1986, PA 2932
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000293
    - Guthrie, Gwen, 1988, PA 2933
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000294
    - Guthrie, Gwen, circa 1980s, PA 2934
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000295
    - Guy Called Gerald, 1990, PA 2935
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000296
    - Guy, Jasmine, 1990, PA 2936
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000297
    - Gyrlz, 1988, PA 2937
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000298
    - Hackford, Taylor
      SEE PHOTOS UNDER: Chuck Berry Hail! Hail! Rock 'n' Roll
    - Haley, Bill
      SEE: Little Richard and Bill Haley
    - Hall, Eramus
      SEE: Eramus Hall
    - Hall, Randy, circa 1988, PA 2939
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000300
    - Hall, Randy, 1984 July, PA 2940
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000301
    - Hammer, M. C., 1989, PA 2941
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000302
    - Hammer, M. C., 1990, PA 2942
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000303
    - Hammer, M. C., 1988, PA 2943
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000304
    - Hammer, M. C., 1991, PA 2944
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000305
    - Hammer, M. C., 1990, PA 2945
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000306
    - Hancock, Herbie, 1984, PA 2947
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000308
    - Hancock, Herbie, 1984, PA 2948
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000309
    - Hancock, Herbie, 1984, PA 2949
      http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAC9726/VAC9726-000310